# **Emeka Okwor**

A creative software engineer and a javascript enthusiast offering 3+ years of experience building software applications with Javascript. Skilled in developing and building multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a software engineer.

Lagos State, Nigeria, NG.

+2348163955616

Email: emekaokwor@outlookl.com GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/chubbvst">https://github.com/chubbvst</a>

rings

Portfolio: https://emekaokwor.tech LinkedIn:https://linkedin.com/in/e mekaokwor

## **EXPERIENCE**

SeamlessHR, Lagos — Frontend Engineer Tech Stack: Vue.

JUNE 2022 - Present

• Part of the frontend team building and maintaining the SeamlessHR Application

**Decagon**, Lagos — Associate Software Engineer

Link: https://decagonhq.com/fellowship/

Link: https://decagon.institute/

**Tech Stack**: Javascript, React, Vuejs, Node Js.

NOVEMBER 2020 - JUNE 2022

- A member of the frontend team managing development projects from initial design through completion, optimizing all cross-browser and multi-platform compatibility.
- *A member of the frontend team developing and maintaining the* Decagon Enterprise app.
- Conversant with Agile methodologies.

Krystal Lab Solutions, Lagos — Junior Fullstack Developer

Tech Stack: Angular, React, Vue, Node Js.

JULY 2019 - MARCH 2020

- *Designed, built, and maintained clients' websites*
- Worked closely with the development team to proffer solutions and decide on technologies to use.
- *Gained more exposure to developing real-life applications.*

**Simba Travels and Logistics,** Lagos — Junior Web Developer

Tech Stack: PHP, Javascript, VUE, Angular

MAY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019

- Built and maintained company website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, and PHP.
- Part of a team that built the staff portal with PHP and VUE.

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

- React Js
- Vue Js
- Angular
- Node Js
- **Express Framework**
- **Typescript**
- Javascript
- **JQuery**
- HTML 5
- CSS<sub>3</sub>
- SASS
- Vuetify
- Material UI
- Tailwind
- GraphQL
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- **MYSQL**
- Firebase
- Version Control with Git and GitHub.
- Docker
- CI (Travis CI)
- Test-Driven Development.
- **Cypress**
- Jest
- Mocha

#### **LEARNING & BOOTCAMPS**

**Andela DevC core track,** Lagos — Fullstack Developer

Project Link: https://teamplay-app-e48a7.firebaseapp.com/

MAY 2019 - JULY 2019 Tech Stack: Node JS, VUE

Moat Academy Lagos - Fullstack Development

JANUARY 2018 - MARCH 2018 Tech Stack: PHP, Javascript

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

## **MUSIC BOX:**

A music streaming web App,

Technologies Used - React.Js, Node Js, Typescript, SASS, MongoDB.

**Link:** https://themusicbox.netlify.app/

#### **PUNTER-MASTERS:**

A social app for bettors or punters.

**Technologies Used** – Vue, Vuetify, Node JS, Express, Firebase, Paystack,

and flutterwave integration

**Link:** https://punter-masters.web.app

## **SCRUM POKER GAME:**

An interactive scrum poker pointer game.

**Technologies:** Vue 3, Node JS, Express, socket.io, Typescript, MongoDB.

Link: https://scrumpokagame.herokuapp.com/

# **JOB FINDER:**

A Job portal where users can search and apply for jobs, using categories like

Technology, Manufacturing, etc. Employers can also post jobs.

Technologies Used - React.Js, Node Js, Typescript, MongoDB.

Link: <a href="https://job-finder-2.netlify.app/">https://job-finder-2.netlify.app/</a>

# **EDUCATION**

## Federal University Of Tech, Owerri, Nigeria

Bachelor of Science in Food Science, May 2011

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC) - SCRUMstudy - Accreditation Body for Scrum and Agile

Vue Js 2 the complete guide - Udemy

Learn About Agile Project Management and SCRUM - OpenClassrooms